February 21st, we have the invocation by Pastor Jonathan Jennings.
Father, I just want to thank you for the opportunity to open this meeting.
Lord, I thank you for a city council that recognizes the need to have you involved.
Lord, I pray that you would just guide and direct and give wisdom,
Lord, as this council makes decisions that will affect the lives of the citizens.
Lord, I pray that each and every person would just have the citizens in their heart,
and I just believe, Lord God, in the council that we have before us.
Father, I pray a blessing over them and a blessing over the meeting,
and I declare this in Jesus' mighty name. Amen.
Amen.
Join me in the pledge.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
All right.
Number four, public input and understanding.
Unscheduled appearances.
We have none.
Number five, consent agenda.
They ask that we approve items six and seven.
So moved.
Second.
Council.
Aye.
Sunberg.
Easton.
Aye.
Williams.
Which is your call?
C.
Item number eight, budget amendment 23-17B,
moving capital improvement unbudgeted carryover monies to MSUA fund
to purchase.
110 North Main Street property.
Good evening.
This budget amendment is pretty much what you just exactly read.
We're just transferring.
We transferred funds, which we'll talk about on the city side.
We transferred funds, and then we're putting them into the infrastructure
for the purchase of that property.
There was a note, and I know that you can see it on your packet.
It had previously said,
110 North Main, but this is for 124,
and that correction's been made on your packet.
Thank you.
Is it?
I've done it.
Okay.
I apologize.
So what's on the paper is correct?
110.
Okay.
It must be on the city side.
I apologize that it's changed on that.
Any other questions for Jennifer?
110 what?
North Main?
North Main.
Where's that?
It's on Main Street.
Thank you.
What building?
What property?
That's the one at 110.
The church.
Listen, Bless.
Church.
Okay.
Thank you.
What is the name of it?
Paysetters.
See, there you go.
That's all you had to say.
Shut up.
That's enough.
Hey, listen.
I'm in the seat tonight.
They told me I was in charge.
Any other questions?
I'll make a motion to approve.
Thank you.
Don't call.
Aye.
Williams.
Easton.
Aye.
Selberg.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, Donkey.
Number nine, action item.
Goodell, Stratton, and Edmonds, and Palmer claim for GRDA
relicensing in the amount of $5,364.
So, these are four professional services by Goodell, Stratton,
primarily going towards the legal process and consulting on the GRDA
for relicensing.
So, everything that we were working on back in December and January,
up to including starting to work on the town hall and some that we had going back and forth
that Larry had been helping us with.
I'm assuming we'll see more bills for the town hall later.
We will see more bills for the town hall if they can bring it up, obviously, since
we have so many people involved.
All right.
Any questions for Mr. Reese?
Motion to approve.
Say it.
Stone Hall.
Aye.
Williams.
Silver.
Aye.
Roth.
Number ten, other than any other new business which has arisen since the posting of this
agenda, it could not have been anticipated prior to the time of posting.
Nothing.
Number 11, staff reports.
Number 12, trustee community announcements.
Number 13, this meeting will be continued from the council chambers and reconvened in the
staff room for the purposes of executive session at the completion of agenda item 15 for the
regular meeting of the Miami City Council.